The most important program on your computer
is your web browser-- and yet most people
aren't sure which web browser they're using
or what a web browser even is.
Let me try to explain by first telling you
what a web browser is not.
A web browser is different from Windows or
Mac, which are systems that allow you to manage
files and programs.
And it's different from a search engine, which
is a website that is used to search the Internet.
Instead, a web browser is a program on your
computer that allows you to visit websites.
You get to your web browser by clicking on
its icon.
From there, you enter web addresses and the
web browser displays the web pages for you.
The web browser is the most important piece
of software on your computer because every
web page runs through it.
So a faster web browser means that you'll
save time on every web page you open.
Installing a new web browser is free and only
takes minutes.
So take a moment to choose a web browser that
you like best today.